Espy, Watt; Papers apap301
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1929-2001; Undated; 9; 14.4 cubic ft.; 14.4 cu. ft.
  - Old Timers Wild West, 1975-1976 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Old Timers Wild West, 1976-1977 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Old Trails, 1977-1978 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Old West, 1964-1965 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Old West, 1964-1965 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Old West, 1966-1967 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 24)
  - Old West, 1967-1968 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Old West, 1969 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Old West, 1969-1970 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Old West, 1970-1971 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Old West, 1971-1972 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Old West, 1973-1978 (Box 89 (9-Publications), Folder 5-6)
  - Old West, 1979-1980 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Old West, 1980-1981 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Old West, 1982-1984 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Old West, 1984 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Old West, 1985; 1988 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Old West, 1992-1993 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Old West, 1994-1995 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Old West, 1995-1996 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Old West, 1996-1997 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Old West, 1997-1998 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Old West, 1998-1999 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Police Detective, 1977-1978 (Box 81 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Police Detective, 1971; 1973; 1976 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Police Files, 1955 June (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - The Police Marksman, 1983 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Pioneer West, 1971; 1974 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Pioneer West, 1975-1976 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Pioneer West, 1976 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Real Detective, 1972-1974 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Real Police Stories, 1954 October (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Real West, 1969 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Real West, 1971-1972 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Real West, 1972-1973; 1975; 1982 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Real West, 1977-1978 (Box 90 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Real West, 1985-1986 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Real West, 1986-1988 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Real West, 1986; 1988-1989 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Revealing Detective, 1945 August (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Sensation, 1943 January (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Serial Killers & Mass Murder Cards, 1992 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Special Detective Cases, 1942 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Star Detective Cases, 1951 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Startling Detective, 1998 March-1999 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Startling Detective, 1999 July-2000 (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Startling Detective, 2000-2001 January (Box 82 (9-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Timely Detective, 1950 March (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - TRUE, 1938; 1940 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - True Action Detective, 1974; 1975 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - True Cases of Yard, 1937 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - True Crime, 1943; 1965 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - True Crime Detective, 1971 April (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - True Detective, 1943; 1947; 1961 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - True Detective, 1961 December; 1962 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - True Frontier, 1967; 1969 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - True Frontier, 1970-1971 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - True Frontier, 1971-1972 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - True Frontier, 1973 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - True Frontier, 1974-1975 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - True Frontier, 1975-1976 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - True Frontier, 1976-1977 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - True Frontier, 1977-1978 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - True Police Cases, 1947 September-1951 (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - True Police Cases, 1953 May-1954 September (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 18)
  - True Police Cases, 1955 July-1956 May (Box 83 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - True Police Cases, 1957; 1961; 1997 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - True Police Cases, 1998 February-1999 February (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - True Police Cases, 1999 June-2000 February (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - True Police Cases, 2000 June-2000 December (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - True Thrills, 1941-1942 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - True West, 1962-1963 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - True West, 1963-1964 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - True West, 1967 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - True West, 1967-1968 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - True West, 1968 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - True West, 1969-1974 (Box 90 (9-Publications), Folder 2-4)
  - True West, 1975 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - True West, 1975-1976 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - True West, 1976-1977 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - True West, 1977-1978 (Box 90 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - True West, 1978-1979 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - True West, 1979 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - True West, 1980 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - True West, 1980-1981 (Box 84 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - True West, 1981 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - True West, 1981-1982 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - True West, 1983 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 3-4)
  - True West, 1984 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 5-7)
  - True West, 1984-1985 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - True West, 1985 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - True West, 1985-1986 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - True West, 1986 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - True West, 1986-1987 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - True West, 1992-1993 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - True West, 1993 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - True West, 1994 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - True West, 1994-1995 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - True West, 1995-1996 (Box 85 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - True West, 1996 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - True West, 1996-1997 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - True West, 1997 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 3-4)
  - True West, 1997-1998 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - True West, 1998 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 6-7)
  - True West, 1998-1999 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - True West, 1999 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - True West, 2000 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Uncensored Detective, 1947 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Uncensored Detective, 1952 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Underworld Detective, 1949; 1957 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Vital Detective, 1954 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - The West, 1968 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - The West, 1969-1970 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - The West, 1970-1971 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - The West, 1971-1972 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Westerner, 1969-1970 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Westerner, 1970-1971 (Box 86 (9-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Westerner, 1971 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Westerner, 1972 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Westerner, 1973 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 3-4)
  - Westerner, 1974 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Westerner, 1975 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Westerner, 1976 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Western Frontier: Bad Men and the Old West and Outlaws and the Old West, 1974-1975 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Western Frontier Presents Outlaws and Gunslingers, 1985-1986 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Western Frontier, 1977-1978 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Western Frontier, 1976-1977 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Western Frontier, 1978 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Wild West, 1986; 1991-1993 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Wild West, 1993-1994 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Wild West, 1994 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Wild West, 1995 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 16-17)
  - Wild West, 1955; 1966 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Women in Crime, 1945; 1947; 1957 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Zane Grey Western, 1971-1972 (Box 87 (9-Publications), Folder 20)
- Espy Project Datasets, 2016-2020
  Contains CSV datasets of American executions created during the Espy Project. Sets will be released by state over the course of the project. Information about the data fields is available here.
  Biographical / Historical
  In 2016, the Council on Library and Information Resources (CLIR) funded The Digital Archive of Executions in the United States, 1608-2002: Digitization and Access to the M. Watt Espy Papers to digitize the index card summaries and reference material and make them available online. The Project attempted to digitize the index card summaries and the reference materials from the Espy Papers and unify them with the Espy File dataset created from the collection during the 1980s.
  - Executions Data from all completed states, 2020 March
    Includes Alaska, Alabama, Hawaii, Oregon, and Wyoming
  - Alaska Executions Data, 2020 March
  - Alabama Executions Data, 2020 March
  - Hawaii Executions Data, 2020 March
  - Oregon Executions Data, 2020 March
  - Wyoming Executions Data, 2020 March